const harryPotterQuizData = [
    {
        QuizName: "Harry Potter"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "1",
        Question: "What is the castle that Harry attends?",
        Options: ["Beauxbaton", "Hogwarts", "Durmstrang", "Ilvermorny"],
        Answer: "Hogwarts"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "2",
        Question: "Who was headmaster at Hogwarts before Dumbledore?",
        Options: ["Dexter Fortescue", "Dilys Derwent", "Phineas Nigellus Black", "Armando Dippet"],
        Answer: "Armando Dippet"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "3",
        Question: "In the later books, Buckbeak gets a secret name in order to protect his identity. What was this nickname?",
        Options: ["Witherwings", "Griphook", "Hokey", "Billywig"],
        Answer: "Witherwings"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "4",
        Question: "Who was Aragog's wife?",
        Options: ["Ungoliant", "Kelpie", "Mosag", "Matagot"],
        Answer: "Mosag"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "5",
        Question: "Who was the Ministry of Magic employee who investigates Morfin's crimes?",
        Options: ["Bob Ogden", "Yaxley", "Kingsley Shacklebolt", "Ludovic Bagman"],
        Answer: "Bob Ogden"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "6",
        Question: "What was Rita Skeeter's animagus form?",
        Options: ["Cat", "Beetle", "Mouse", "Bird"],
        Answer: "Beetle"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "7",
        Question: "Who was the leader of the Centaur's?",
        Options: ["Magorian", "Firenze", "Bane", "Ronan"],
        Answer: "Magorian"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "8",
        Question: "Which of Voldemort's Death Eaters was an unspeakable?",
        Options: ["Antonin Dolohov", "Thorfinn Rowle", "Scabior", "Augustus Rookwood"],
        Answer: "Augustus Rookwood"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "9",
        Question: "What is the magic number that appears all throughout the Harry Potter story?",
        Options: ["5", "8", "7", "3"],
        Answer: "7"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "10",
        Question: "How many staircases are in Hogwarts?",
        Options: ["142", "100", "150", "200"],
        Answer: "142"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "11",
        Question: "What vault number do Hagrid and Harry stop at first in the Philosopher's Stone?",
        Options: ["687", "713", "394", "777"],
        Answer: "713"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "12",
        Question: "Who planted the Whomping Willow?",
        Options: ["Lupin", "Dumbledore", "Dippet", "Merlin"],
        Answer: "Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "13",
        Question: "What is Dumbledore's full name?",
        Options: ["Albus Wulfric Brian Percival Dumbledore", "Albus Percival Brian Wulfric Dumbledore", "Albus Brian Wulfric Percival Dumbledore", "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore"],
        Answer: "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "14",
        Question: "What are the small pale-green skinned creatures that reside in the black Lake alongside the Merpeople and the Giant squid?",
        Options: ["Flobberworm", "Kelpie", "Grindylow", "Marmite"],
        Answer: "Grindylow"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "15",
        Question: "Who was Ollivander's competition in making and selling wands?",
        Options: ["Mykew Gregorovitch", "Gellert Grindelwald", "Rolanda Hooch", "Aurora Sinistra"],
        Answer: "Mykew Gregorovitch"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "16",
        Question: "Who killed Helena Ravenclaw?",
        Options: ["Fat Friar", "Bloody Baron", "Cuthbert Binns", "Sir Nicholas de Mimsey Porpington"],
        Answer: "Bloody Baron"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "17",
        Question: "How many years had passed between the first opening of the Chamber of Secrets and the second?",
        Options: ["50", "100", "150", "200"],
        Answer: "50"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "18",
        Question: "What page does Snape have the students turn to when he teaches a class of Defence Against the Dark Arts in Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        Options: ["200", "687", "567", "394"],
        Answer: "394"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "19",
        Question: "How many Sickles equals one Galleon?",
        Options: ["29", "15", "17", "10"],
        Answer: "17"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "20",
        Question: "Who gave the original prophecy involving Harry and Voldemort?",
        Options: ["Sybill Trelawney", "Albus Dumbledore", "Serious Black", "Minerva McGonagall"],
        Answer: "Sybill Trelawney"
    }
]